<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Philipp Antar</title>
    <link>https://philippantar.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Philipp Antar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://philippantar.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One way to create animations of Keras models learning</title>
      <link>https://philippantar.com/posts/one-way-to-generate-animations-with-keras/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philippantar.com/posts/one-way-to-generate-animations-with-keras/</guid>
      <description>Say you want to create an animation that shows how a neural network learns from data. Maybe something like this, where a neural network learns the shape of a sine function:
 Here&amp;rsquo;s how I did that. First, get the code for the neural network, so you can follow along: ml-sine on GitHub
When training your model you&amp;rsquo;ll usually use a statement like this:
model.fit(x_train, y_train, batch_size=128, epochs=100) After every epoch we want to take a snapshot of how well our prediction fits the training data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I deploy to GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://philippantar.com/posts/how-i-deploy-to-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 12:25:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philippantar.com/posts/how-i-deploy-to-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>How does Github pages work? (skip if you know this) Many static pages generators will generate a single public as output. This folders contains the entire generated site. On GitHub you can create a repository with the special name &amp;lt;your GitHub username&amp;gt;.github.io, in my case p886.github.io. Doing so will create a webpage at the address http://github_user_name.github.io.
The problem with static page generators and GitHub pages The tricky part is that the master branch of that repository should contain the site (the content of the aforementioned public folder), while on the other hand you probably want to keep the source files of that page (in my case of collection of markdown files) in the same repository.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>